

Ahmed Yousry

web developer

Phone: +201276794081

Address: Faculty of Fine Arts, 64 Mostafa Fahmy St., Glim, Alexandria.

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayousry30/

Email: ayousry943@gmail.com

Motivated PHP Developer seeks employment as part of a dynamic software development team. Fluent in several programming languages. - More Than 3 Years Experience as PHP web Developer . 1 Years Experience as technical support at Te Data . Highlights

Experience building a variety of different web applications and websites

and have a variety of different skills like Ceh certification Mcsa windows server 2008 certification Strong with MySQL Good in laravel Good in Django Good in mongodb Fluent in python and AWS Fluent in devops Fluent in Docker Fluent

in elasticsearch Very familiar with solid principles

EXPERIENCE

EDLF 06/2015-10/2015

Diver master

Responsible For Teaching Diving.

Telecom Egypt 01/2016 - 06/2016

Technical support

Responsible for repairing networks, computer hardware and repairing Internet clients.

Maptec 02/2017 – 01/2019

php developer

Created company website www.maptecgroup.com and responsible for its updating.

Created and developed a database

Created and developed a CRM System and responsible for its updating.

ierek 02/2019-10/2019

Sinior Php Developer

Responsible for managing a team of developers and the company website, Open Journal Systems, WordPress Blog with maintaining and adding new feature

EZMEA 11/2019-4/2019

Sinior Php Developer

EDUCATION

alexandria university

management information system

SKILLS

AWS & WHM &Devops & openshift & Docker & kubernetes & helm & grafana & prometheus & Ansible & vagrant & web security & penetration testing & kali linux

& elasticsearch & Haproxy & kibana & chef & redis & lamp & mongodb &

CI/CD & jenkins & PostgreSQL & mysql & php native & Laravel & python

Nodejs & Reactjs & Git & Slim & solid principles & web scraping & design pattern & Django & Google Api & Facbook Api & agile & WebSocket & Microservices & test driven development & service oriented architecture

Created using Resumonk - Online Resume Builder

PROJECTS

Backage for laravel panal

https://packagist.org/packages/yousry943/easyadmin

EasyAdmin is a great admin to use multi authentication, multi language, multi email template.

Don't create new admin panel when you start a new project just use it

Ci/Cd on kubernetes

https://drive.google.com/file/d/lynM_zrK3ZkDO6q_bezw87soJtl038ygI/view

Ecommerce builder

https://weblic.me/

Add Some Features In System And Complete It

Created by (codeigniter)

Tracking System

https://tracking.system.ierek.net/

File storage System

https://file.system.ierek.net/public/login

CRM System

https://crm.system.ierek.net/public/login

Submition System

https://www.ierek.net/

laravel

http://kryptonmotion.com/

laravel

www.acl-egypt.com

laravel

http://ierek.com/

wordpress

https://elephantsink.com/

php native

https://alljobnow.com

php native

https://www.lesflux.com/

python project

http://iwosstm.net/

python project

http://osdss.net/

open journal system

https://press.ierek.com/

system real estate

http://estasmer.com/system/angular/pages- login.php

Education system (laravel)

http://18.224.29.119/alex/admin/login

CERTIFICATIONS

ceh

eccouncil

ccna

Cisco

ccna security

Cisco

MCSA windows server 2008

microsoft

linux+

comptia

security +

comptia

RECOMMENDATIONS

ahmed elbehary

CEO MAPTEC

Everyone has the skills these skills appear only in a good environment, and good managers i was lucky and i thanks my god to know Mr:ahmed and Mr:eslam there are helped me alot when i got job php developer in Maptec company without any experiences

i cant forget who helped me when i was not know code well its too hard to find persons like Mr :ahmed and Mr:eslam i will available anytime and anywhere when Maptec company needs me I wish every success to Mr:eslam and Mr:ahmed

Mohamed Adel

web developer

i worked at Maptec and Ahmad was the team leader. He is good in leadership and management. He is serious about work, he likes to

work and learn all the new features and we have formed a good team together and I still have it with him and i wish him all success

IEREK Institute

Ahmed stayed with us in IEREK for almost one year, and in that year we can't deny the fact that he made a lot of things easier for us. He was efficient and adhered to his deadlines. He took care of our website and solved as many issues as possible, and we couldn't have asked for a better knowledgable and passionate developer. It was unfortunate that he left us for a better opportunity in the developing world, but we still have an on going relationship where he resolves issues for us remotly, even without asking for anything in return. If you are looking for someone that you could leave everything in their hands and be assured that everything will get done in a timely and efficient manner... then you have found him.

Manager of Ierek

To whom it may concern, This is to say that Ahmed was one of the most valuable team players in our company, i enjoyed working with him on a personal level and ona professional one. He's knowledgable and even if it is something new to him, he could get around it very easily. He was an asset and it was really regretable to have him go because he had a better offer. I wish him the best, Regards,

| LANGUAGES | | |
|-----------------|--|--|
| English, Arabic | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |
| | | |